<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MLSTAT 2023</title>
    <link>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MLSTAT 2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/overview/</guid>
      <description>Organized by Bruce Eckel August 15-19, 2022 (Formerly The Java Posse Roundup)
NOTE: Many companies are still not supporting travel to conferences, so the event this Summer has become a developer retreat, which is a smaller and far less formal gathering. It does not have an entrance fee, because we will not be using the Parish Hall as we usually do. In addition, we will not be following the schedule on this site, but will organically be creating discussions, workshops to explore particular topics, and outdoor activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Outdoor activities will be in the morning, sessions in the afternoon (when it often rains) Pre-conference: If you arrive early, post something on Slack. If I or others are around and available, we might be able to come out for meals or other activities.
Post-conference: Often people stay the day after the conference or for the weekend; informal gatherings have been known to happen.
Sunday 6:00pm Welcome Potluck Barbeque at Bruce&amp;rsquo;s House (107 WhiteRock).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee</title>
      <link>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-stat.github.io/MLSTAT2023/committee/</guid>
      <description> General Chair: Zhihuang Zhang and Aoying Zhou Pronouns and whether photos are ok Group picture on Thursday during a morning session break Butterflies and bumblebees. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking it&amp;rsquo;ll be over soon&amp;hellip; Private feedback, public reflection Would you be interested in some difficult feedback? Explicit permission to take care of yourself. Law of two feet writ large. Eyes forward conference presentation is about the happy path. We talk about problems and challenges Badge space so people don&amp;rsquo;t worry about forgetting badges </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
